Class of 1894 Records, 1823-1977
Smith College Archives
Class of 1894 Records
1823-1977
Smith College. Class of 1894.
RG 80 UUID:57ea8c73-a113-44f5-9672-abe284c28f46
15 boxes (6 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in fifteen boxes and contains black and white photographs, photo albums, correspondence, letters, scrapbooks, class notes, student papers and drawings, writings, publications, newspaper clippings, record books and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1894.
The Class of 1894 was the sixteenth entering class and the sixteenth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class Years 1894 records, 1823-1977, contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1894. Types of materials include black and white photographs, photo albums, correspondence, letters, scrapbooks, class notes, student papers and drawings, writings, publications, newspaper clippings, record books and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1894.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1894 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1894: Class Baby 1931 (Box 1482, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Class Letters 1939-40, 1944, 1946, 1948-50, 1952-53, 1955-57 (Box 1482, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Class History, Class Lists 1948-49, 1951, undated (Box 1482, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Class Photo Book 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Class Supper 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Commencement 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Commencement Music 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Commencement Photographs 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Commencement Speaker 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Group Photographs 1890, 1894, undated (Box 1482, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Ivy Day 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Ivy Day Photographs 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Junior Prom 1893 (Box 1482, Folder 13)
- Class of 1894: Junior Reception 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 14)
- Class of 1894: Junior Ushers 1893 (Box 1482, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894: Obituaries 1929, 1932-33, 1937, 1939, 1946-50, undated (Box 1482, Folder 16)
- Class of 1894: Senior Dramatics 1894 (Box 1482, Folder 17)
- Class of 1894: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) 1894 (Box 1482.1, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Songs undated (Box 1482.1, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Sophomore Reception 1890 (Box 1482.1, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Unidentified Photographs undated (Box 1482.1, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Reunions 1954, undated (Box 1483, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1895 1895 (Box 1483, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1897 1897 (Box 1483, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1899 1899 (Box 1483, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1904 1904 (Box 1483, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1909 1909 (Box 1483, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1914 1914 (Box 1483, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1919 1919 (Box 1483, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1924 1924 (Box 1483, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1925 1925 (Box 1483, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1929 1929 (Box 1483, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1934 1934 (Box 1483, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1939 1939 (Box 1483, Folder 13)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1944 (Correspondence with Class Secretary, Letters for Class Book) 1944 (Box 1483, Folder 14)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1944 1944 (Box 1483, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1944 (Class Book typescript) 1944 (Box 1483, Folder 16)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1949 1949 (Box 1483, Folder 17)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1954 1954 (Box 1483, Folder 18)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-1959 1959 (Box 1483, Folder 19)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-Reunion Photographs undated (Box 1483, Folder 20)
- Class of 1894: Reunions-Reunion Songs undated (Box 1483, Folder 21)
- Class of 1894: Class Secretary-Record Book 1890-1929 (Box 1484, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1930s 1930, 1932-35, 1937-39 (Box 1484, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1944 Jan-May 1944 (Box 1484, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1944 Jun-Dec 1944 (Box 1484, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1945-49 1945-1949 (Box 1484, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1950 1950 (Box 1484, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1951-54 1951-1954 (Box 1484, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-Miscellaneous undated (Box 1484, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Alumnae Council Reports 1931-37, 1939-41, 1946, 1948, undated (Box 1484, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Alumnae Fund Letters 1943-45, 1947-48, 1951-54 (Box 1484, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Treasurer's Records-Correspondence 1949-1951 (Box 1484, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Treasurer's Records-Ledger Book 1890-1951 (Box 1484, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Allen, Sarah Theodosia (Photographs) undated (Box 1485, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Anderson, Grace Estey (Correspondence, etc) 1891, 1895, 1949, 1958, undated (Box 1485, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Andrews, Katharine Hannah (Correspondence) 1952, undated (Box 1485, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Andrews, Katharine Hannah (Photographs, etc) 1894, 1925, 1958, undated (Box 1485, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Atwood, Alice Chapman 1896, 1945, undated (Box 1485, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Balch, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs) 1894, undated (Box 1485, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Bancroft, Frances Marsh undated (Box 1485, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Bauer, Olive Mary (Photographs) undated (Box 1485, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Bawden, Sarah Elisabeth (Photographs) 1894 (Box 1485, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Brown, Inez (Photographs) 1894 (Box 1485, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Brown, Ophelia Sanger (Photographs) undated (Box 1485, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Browne, Frances Eliza (Correspondence) 1954 (Box 1485, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Browne, Helen Swale (Photographs) 1894 (Box 1485, Folder 13)
- Class of 1894: Browne, Helen Swale (Photographs) 1894 (Box 1485, Folder 14)
- Class of 1894: Burrington, Venila Spaulding (Correspondence) 1950, 1954 (Box 1485, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894: Chapman, Elizabeth Kimball (Correspondence) 1954, undated (Box 1485, Folder 16)
- Class of 1894: Chapman, Elizabeth Kimball (Photographs) 1894, undated (Box 1485, Folder 17)
- Class of 1894: Chapman, Marguerite Elisabeth undated (Box 1485, Folder 18)
- Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Correspondence) 1890, 1892-94, 1898, undated (Box 1485, Folder 19)
- Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Photographs, etc) 1890, 1894, 1896, 1900, 1963, undated (Box 1485, Folder 20)
- Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Student Papers) 1892-94, undated (Box 1485, Folder 21)
- Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Student Papers) 1892-93, undated (Box 1485, Folder 22)
- Class of 1894: Clough, Anna Grace (Correspondence) 1958 (Box 1485, Folder 23)
- Class of 1894: Covel, Abbie Walker 1949, undated (Box 1485, Folder 24)
- Class of 1894: Coyle, Susan Edmond (Photographs) 1894, undated (Box 1485, Folder 25)
- Class of 1894: Davis, Alice Abigail 1950 (Box 1486, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Davis, Mary Isabella (Account Book, Photographs) 1887-88, 1890-93, undated (Box 1486, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: De Ridder, Belle (Correspondence) 1959 (Box 1486, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: De Ridder, Belle (Photographs) undated (Box 1486, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Devin, Ethel Wyatt (Correspondence) 1952-59, undated (Box 1486, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Devin, Ethel Wyatt (Photographs) undated (Box 1486, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Dickerman, Elizabeth Street (Photographs) 1910, 1919 (Box 1486, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Dunbar, Olivia Howard (Photographs, Writings) 1894, 1903-05, 1907, 1909-11, 1915, 1922, undated (Box 1486, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Dunbar, Olivia Howard (Writings) 1903, 1905, 1907-10, 1913-15, 1919, 1921, 1924 (Box 1486, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Dickerman, Elizabeth Street (Writings) 1917-19, 1921, 1923, undated (Box 1486, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Dustin, Anne Rogers (Photographs) 1893-94 (Box 1486, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Eastman, Mary Bentley (Correspondence) 1958, undated (Box 1487, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Evans, Laura Livingston (Photographs) undated (Box 1487, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Fairbanks, Charlotte (Photographs, etc) 1922, 1932, undated (Box 1487, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Fletcher, Elizabeth Le Baron 1951, 1967 (Box 1487, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: French, Marian Leslie 1945 (Box 1487, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: French, Marian Leslie (Photographs) undated (Box 1487, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Frost, Mary Pepperell (Box 1487, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Fuller, Mary Breese (Photographs, etc) 1900, 1902, 1904, 1911, 1915, undated (Box 1487, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Gale, Marion 1951-52, undated (Box 1487, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Photographs) undated (Box 1487, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Index) 1890-1894 (Box 1487, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1890) 1890 (Box 1487, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Nov 1890-Mar 1892) 1890-1892 (Box 1487, Folder 13)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-May 1892-Sept 1893) 1892-1893 (Box 1487, Folder 14)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Oct-Dec 1893) 1893 (Box 1487, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Jan-Mar 1894) 1894 (Box 1487, Folder 16)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Apr-Jun 1894) 1894 (Box 1487, Folder 17)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Aug-Oct 1890) 1890 (Box 1487, Folder 18)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Nov 1890-Jan 1892) 1890-1892 (Box 1487, Folder 19)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Mar 1892-Oct 1893) 1892-1893 (Box 1487, Folder 20)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Nov 1893-Jan 1894) 1893-1894 (Box 1487, Folder 21)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Feb-Jun 1894) 1894 (Box 1487, Folder 22)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Course Notes) 1893 (Box 1487, Folder 23)
- Class of 1894: Graves, Katherine Olive (Photographs) 1894, 1914, 1917 (Box 1487, Folder 24)
- Class of 1894: Greenough, Clara Mary 1951-54, 1957, 1959, undated (Box 1487, Folder 25)
- Class of 1894: Greenough, Clara Mary (Certificates) 1918-19, 1923-24, 1930-31, 1934 (Box 1487, Folder 26)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Box 1487, Folder 27)
- Class of 1894: Hammond, Juliet (Correspondence) 1954 (Box 1487, Folder 28)
- Class of 1894: Harkness, Edith Alice 1951, undated (Box 1487, Folder 29)
- Class of 1894: Hart, Helen Marguerite (Photographs) 1893-94, undated (Box 1487, Folder 30)
- Class of 1894: Hartwell, Mary Ann 1946 (Box 1487, Folder 31)
- Class of 1894: Hartwell, Mary Ann (Photographs, etc) 1913-15, 1922-23, 1925, 1939, 1943, undated (Box 1487, Folder 32)
- Class of 1894: Herrick, A(da) Elizabeth (Photographs, etc) 1823, 1826, 1843, 1845-46, 1867, 1870, 1873, 1905, 1914, 1919, 1922, 1945, undated (Box 1487, Folder 33)
- Class of 1894: Hubbard, Alice Clark (Correspondence) 1954, undated (Box 1487, Folder 34)
- Class of 1894: Hubbard, Alice Clark (Photographs) undated (Box 1487, Folder 35)
- Class of 1894: Humphrey, Mary King (Box 1487, Folder 36)
- Class of 1894: Ingram, Lucy Belle 1911 (Box 1487, Folder 37)
- Class of 1894: Johnson, Eleanor Hope (Photographs, etc) 1891, 1902, 1911, 1920, 1927, 1935-36, 1942-45, 1947, 1949-51, 1953-55, 1963-64, undated (Box 1487, Folder 38)
- Class of 1894: Jones, Ellen Permelia 1944 (Box 1487, Folder 39)
- Class of 1894: Jones, Ellen Permelia (Photographs) undated (Box 1487, Folder 40)
- Class of 1894: Kimball, Martha Hayward (Photographs) undated (Box 1487, Folder 41)
- Class of 1894: Lamb, Lucy Inez (Correspondence) 1950-59 (Box 1488, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Lamb, Lucy Inez (Photographs) 1959, undated (Box 1488, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Lambert, Helen Bordman (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Leach, Alice Lydia (Correspondence) undated (Box 1488, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Learned, Agnes Wakefield (Photographs) 1888, undated (Box 1488, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Leighton, Emma Elizabeth 1899, 1904-05, 1908 (Box 1488, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Lewis, Mary Delia (Box 1488, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Lockwood, Jeanne Julia (Correspondence) 1951-52, 1954, undated (Box 1488, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Lockwood, Jeanne Julia (Photographs, etc) 1954, undated (Box 1488, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Lyall, Katherine E. (Correspondence-Sept 26, 1890-May 17, 1891) 1890-1891 (Box 1488, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Lynch, Caroline Vinia (Photographs, etc) 1894, 1926, undated (Box 1488, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: McMahan, Una 1906-07, 1909 (Box 1488, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Mann, Clausine 1950, undated (Box 1488, Folder 13)
- Class of 1894: Mansfield, Elizabeth Langley (Correspondence, etc) 1894, 1954 (Box 1488, Folder 14)
- Class of 1894: Mansfield, Elizabeth Langley (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894: Mason, Martha (Correspondence) 1949-51, undated (Box 1488, Folder 16)
- Class of 1894: Mason, Martha (Photographs) 1890-91, 1893-94, 1917-19 (Box 1488, Folder 17)
- Class of 1894: Mead, Stella Baham (Correspondence) 1954 (Box 1488, Folder 18)
- Class of 1894: Merrill, Georgiana (Photographs, etc) 1895, 1916, 1927, 1929, 1945, undated (Box 1488, Folder 19)
- Class of 1894: Merriman, Mabel Lilian (Photographs, etc) 1920-22, undated (Box 1488, Folder 20)
- Class of 1894: Moon, Elizabeth Laetitia 1900-01, 1946 (Box 1488, Folder 21)
- Class of 1894: Moon, Elizabeth Laetitia (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 22)
- Class of 1894: Moore, Mabel Reynolds 1934, 1938, 1950, undated (Box 1488, Folder 23)
- Class of 1894: Morse, Anna Gertrude (Correspondence) 1954 (Box 1488, Folder 24)
- Class of 1894: Noyes, Bertha Lizette (Photographs) 1894, 1896, undated (Box 1488, Folder 25)
- Class of 1894: Oakes, Julia Anna (Photographs) 1894 (Box 1488, Folder 26)
- Class of 1894: Parrish, Margaret Louise (Correspondence) 1951 (Box 1488, Folder 27)
- Class of 1894: Paul, Anne Marie 1894-95, 1951, undated (Box 1488, Folder 28)
- Class of 1894: Peck, Teresina (Correspondence) 1906, 1945-46 (Box 1488, Folder 29)
- Class of 1894: Peck, Teresina (Photographs, etc) 1938, undated (Box 1488, Folder 30)
- Class of 1894: Perkins, Helen (Correspondence) 1897, 1949, 1952, 1956, 1958-59, undated (Box 1488, Folder 31)
- Class of 1894: Pickering, Minnie Maud 1948 (Box 1488, Folder 32)
- Class of 1894: Pickering, Minnie Maud (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 33)
- Class of 1894: Platt, Ada Susan (Correspondence) 1955 (Box 1488, Folder 34)
- Class of 1894: Platt, Ada Susan (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 35)
- Class of 1894: Platt, Clara Boardman (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 36)
- Class of 1894: Pratt, Sarah Marie 1949 (Box 1488, Folder 37)
- Class of 1894: Pratt, Sarah Marie (Photographs) 1892, undated (Box 1488, Folder 38)
- Class of 1894: Prouty, Mable Lucretia (Photographs) 1893-94 (Box 1488, Folder 39)
- Class of 1894: Putney, Mary Phillips (Photographs) (Box 1488, Folder 40)
- Class of 1894: Reynolds, Harriet Lyman (Correspondence) 1936, undated (Box 1488, Folder 41)
- Class of 1894: Rice, Lillian Ballance (Photographs) 1893-94, 1947, undated (Box 1488, Folder 42)
- Class of 1894: Richardson, Belle (Photographs) 1894, 1950, undated (Box 1488, Folder 43)
- Class of 1894: Richardson, Mary Lilias (Box 1488, Folder 44)
- Class of 1894: Robbins, Alice Emily (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 45)
- Class of 1894: Rogers, Annie (Correspondence) 1952, 1954, undated (Box 1488, Folder 46)
- Class of 1894: Rogers, Annie (Photographs) 1893 (Box 1488, Folder 47)
- Class of 1894: Ruger, Harriet Marsh 1944 (Box 1488, Folder 48)
- Class of 1894: Rugg, Harriet Alice (Photographs) undated (Box 1488, Folder 49)
- Class of 1894: Sanford, Stella De Land (Correspondence) 1954 (Box 1489, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Schermerhorn, Rena (Photographs) 1890, 1894 (Box 1489, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Scott, Mary Stuart (Photographs) 1894 (Box 1489, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Searl, Mabel Darrow (Correspondence) 1952 (Box 1489, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Searl, Mabel Darrow (Photographs) 1895, undated (Box 1489, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Seelye, Mabel 1872, 1894 (Box 1489, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Sherrill, Grace Munger (Photographs) 1892, undated (Box 1489, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Sherwood, Tirzah Lovejoy (Photographs) undated (Box 1489, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Smith, Abigail May (Photographs) 1891 (Box 1489, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Smith, Alice Abigail 1892, 1949, undated (Box 1489, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Smith, Grace Angeline (Correspondence) 1950-51, undated (Box 1489, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Smith, Grace Angeline (Photographs) 1894-95, undated (Box 1489, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Swett, Edith Josephine (Photographs) 1893 (Box 1489, Folder 13)
- Class of 1894: Taft, Anna Gleason (Photographs) (Box 1489, Folder 14)
- Class of 1894: Thompson, Caroline Lee Hualani 1937 (Box 1489, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894: Wakelin, Elizabeth undated (Box 1489, Folder 16)
- Class of 1894: Walton, Mabel Lilian 1948 (Box 1489, Folder 17)
- Class of 1894: Warburton, Cora Isabel (Correspondence, etc) undated (Box 1489, Folder 18)
- Class of 1894: Warburton, Cora Isabel (Photographs) undated (Box 1489, Folder 19)
- Class of 1894: Ware, Katharine (Bookplate) 1947-49, 1957 (Box 1489, Folder 20)
- Class of 1894: Ware, Katherine (Photographs, etc) 1917, undated (Box 1489, Folder 21)
- Class of 1894: Watters, Bertha Alice (Correspondence) 1894, 1900, 1948, 1952-54, 1959, undated (Box 1489, Folder 22)
- Class of 1894: Watters, Bertha Alice (Photographs, etc) 1896, undated (Box 1489, Folder 23)
- Class of 1894: Wenham, Grace Putnam 1951 (Box 1489, Folder 24)
- Class of 1894: Wenham, Grace Putnam (Photographs) undated (Box 1489, Folder 25)
- Class of 1894: Whiton, Helen Isabel (Box 1489, Folder 26)
- Class of 1894: Wilder, Bertha Frances (Photographs) undated (Box 1489, Folder 27)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Box 1489, Folder 28)
- Class of 1894: Willard, E(lisa) May (Photographs, etc) 1917, undated (Box 1489, Folder 29)
- Class of 1894: Williams, Sarah Holbrook (Photographs) 1893-94, undated (Box 1489, Folder 30)
- Class of 1894: Wood, Alice Dewey (Photographs) 1891, 1894, undated (Box 1489, Folder 31)
- Class of 1894: Wyman, Helen Lydia undated (Box 1489, Folder 32)
- Class of 1894: Frost, Mary Pepperrell (Photographs, Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1490)
- Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Memorabilia book) Various dates (Box 1491)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Biography and Genealogy) 1886, 1896, 1917, 1948, 1955, 1977, undated (Box 1492, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Biog.-Miscellaneous) 1891-92, 1898, 1921-22, undated (Box 1492, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Bird study and Audubon Society of Rhode Island) 1939, 1942-43, 1949, 1953, undated (Box 1492, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Correspondence) 1885-86, 1910, 1933, 1940-41, undated (Box 1492, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Education-Lyndon Institute, 1887) 1886-87 (Box 1492, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Education-Smith College: Course Lecture Notes) 1890-92, undated (Box 1492, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Education-Smith College: Course Lecture Notes-English Literature) 1890, undated (Box 1492, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Drawings) 1892, undated (Box 1492, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Manuscripts) 1909, 1912, 1925, undated (Box 1492, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Manuscripts-Joel Dunbar) undated (Box 1492, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Photographs) 1908, undated (Box 1492, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Publications) 1888-89, 1901, 1907, 1943 (Box 1492, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Rice, Lillian Balance (Scrapbooks) Various dates (Box 1493)
- Class of 1894: Webster, Letitia / Whiton, Helen Isabel (Photo album, Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1494)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence) 1890-91 (Box 1495, Folder 1)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence, Jan-Apr 1892) 1892 (Box 1495, Folder 2)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence, May-Jun 1892) 1892 (Box 1495, Folder 3)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1892) 1892 (Box 1495, Folder 4)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence, 1893) 1893 (Box 1495, Folder 5)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence-Bragdon, Claude F.) 1900, 1902, 1904, 1906, 1908, undated (Box 1495, Folder 6)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence-Bragdon, Henry) 1891, 1897, 1899-1900, 1904, 1960, 1962, undated (Box 1495, Folder 7)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence) 1895-96 (Box 1495, Folder 8)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence) 1896-97 (Box 1495, Folder 9)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence) 1898-99 (Box 1495, Folder 10)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence) 1903-04 (Box 1495, Folder 11)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence) 1905-07 (Box 1495, Folder 12)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Correspondence-Wilkinson, Josephine) 1891, 1908-09, undated (Box 1495, Folder 13)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (General) 1906-08, 1961, 1964, undated (Box 1495, Folder 14)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Photographs) 1901, 1907, undated (Box 1495, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Published letters) undated (Box 1495, Folder 16)